<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Pratham Blogs</title>
    <link>https://blog.pratham-mishra.in/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Pratham Blogs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 20:16:36 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.pratham-mishra.in/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>COMPUTER GRAPHICS AND ANIMATION TECHNOLOGY Questions And It`s solutions For Exam </title>
      <link>https://blog.pratham-mishra.in/post/computer_graphic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 20:16:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.pratham-mishra.in/post/computer_graphic/</guid>
      <description>COMPUTER GRAPHICS AND ANIMATION TECHNOLOGY Questions And It`s solutions For Exam My Source 📖 For Questions I`m using THIS
Q1. Explain the need of computer graphics in detail. Computer graphics play a crucial role in various fields, ranging from entertainment and gaming to scientific visualization and design. The need for computer graphics stems from its ability to create, manipulate, and display visual content using computers. Here are several key reasons why computer graphics are essential:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Technology Questions And It`s solutions For Exam</title>
      <link>https://blog.pratham-mishra.in/post/web_tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:21:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.pratham-mishra.in/post/web_tech/</guid>
      <description>Web Technology Questions And It`s solutions For Exam My Source 📖 For Questions I`m using THIS
Q1. Explain Head section of HTML with the help of suitable example. The &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; section of an HTML document contains metadata and other information about the HTML document, but it is not displayed on the actual webpage. It typically includes elements like the document title, links to stylesheets or scripts, character encoding, and more. Here&amp;rsquo;s an example of how the &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; section is structured:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Important Question And Its Solution for DBMS Exam</title>
      <link>https://blog.pratham-mishra.in/post/some_imp_questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 00:50:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.pratham-mishra.in/post/some_imp_questions/</guid>
      <description>Some Important Question And Its Solution for DBMS Exam My Source 📖 For Questions I`m using THIS
Q1. What is Data Base Management System? Explain with its Applications. DBMS stands for Database Management System. It is a software system that enables users to create, store, organize, and manage vast amounts of data efficiently and effectively. DBMS provides an interface for interacting with databases and handles tasks such as data storage, retrieval, modification, and deletion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Install Custom Rom In Oneplus 8</title>
      <link>https://blog.pratham-mishra.in/post/custom-rom-on-oneplus8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 23:50:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.pratham-mishra.in/post/custom-rom-on-oneplus8/</guid>
      <description>How To Install Custom Rom In Oneplus 8 What You Need Fastboot &amp;amp; ADB Drivers Unlocked Bootloader Custom Rom and Custom Recovery Installing a custom ROM on your OnePlus 8 involves several steps. Please note that the process may void your warranty and has the potential to damage your device if not done correctly. Make sure to back up your data before proceeding. Here&amp;rsquo;s a general guide to installing a custom ROM on your OnePlus 8:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Unlock Bootloader Oneplus 8</title>
      <link>https://blog.pratham-mishra.in/post/unlock-bootloader-oneplus8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 12:05:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.pratham-mishra.in/post/unlock-bootloader-oneplus8/</guid>
      <description>How To Unlock Bootloader Oneplus 8 What You Need Fastboot &amp;amp; ADB Drivers To unlock the bootloader of your OnePlus 8, you need to follow the official procedure provided by OnePlus. Here are the general steps to unlock the bootloader:
Backup your data: Unlocking the bootloader will erase all data on your device, so it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to back up any important files or data before proceeding.
Enable Developer Options: Go to Settings &amp;gt; About Phone and tap on the &amp;ldquo;Build number&amp;rdquo; seven times to unlock Developer Options.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
